

# Maxim Sheshukov



Berlin, Germany



+4915256004078



sheshukovmaxim@gmail.com



qo-maxus-qo

A results-oriented software engineer with 8 years of work experience. Well-versed in producing efficient, reusable and readable code. Initiative and creative, constantly looking for ways for improvement. Some of my personal projects are Foody (Flutter), Marbles Puzzle (Qt, QML), di (C++).

## Work experience

**Software Engineer C++** 06/2019 - nowadays

Lead Software Engineer C++/Qt 11/2018 - 03/2019

**Software Engineer C++** 01/2018 - 06/2018

**Software Engineer C++/Qt** 10/2017 - 12/2017

**Software Engineer C++/Qt** 03/2016 - 09/2017

Software Engineer C++

11/2013 - 03/2016

BinarySpaces, Berlin, Germany

- Reduced project save time by 50% by implementing data cache in RAM.
- Implemented a release MVP feature Rotary Table for machine setup.

Escape Technology, Moscow, Russia

• Implemented moving avatars like in Telegram messenger.

Luxoft, Moscow, Russia

Added a debugger for Lua scripts.

2GIS, Novosibirsk, Russia

Implemented the algorithm for choosing the fastest server.

Movavi, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Implemented a <u>Slideshow Maker</u> that became a successful product.

SoftLab-NSK, Novosibirsk, Russia

Designed a no bullets <u>biathlon training system</u> for children.

### **Education**

Computer science / Physics master's degree 09/2006 - 06/2012

Novosibirsk State University, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Section of automation of physical and technical research. Department of physics.

#### Skills

Coding

C++, STL, Qt, QML Dart, Flutter Boost ••••• ••••• •••• **Development** 

Git, CI, CD OOP, SOLID, TDD Algorithms, patterns ••••• ••••• Languages

Russian English German



### **Hobbies**



Programming



ΔΙ



Traveling



Dooding



Btw, I use Arch

# **Strengths**

Quick learning

Critical thinking

**Teamwork** 

Reliability

Initiative

Leadership